Hi, it's me and this is my newest catsuit from The Handmaid, a see-through mesh
catsuit and I'm going to try this one on today. I haven't even unpacked it yet, it
was a birthday gift so I'm going to do it now. I always love the packaging.
Here we go. Well it has kind of a velvet print on it and I'm really curious about
the look when I'm going to wear it so I'll change into it.
Okay, that was pretty quick because it's super easy to get into.
The fabric is really stretchy so it's also really comfortable except for the zipper because
zipper is not stretchy so it's a bit short due to the zipper but otherwise it
feels great and it's comfy and stretchy
why do I always do that?
I will just put it away.
Okay, so what I noticed is this really big white tag here.
Probably have to cut it out because yeah you can see it.
And I decided on some plain underwear because I thought well there's going to be a lot of print
And yeah, a lot of stuff going on here on the catsuit itself.
So plain underwear, which I think was a good decision.
Also plain shoes.
So just basic black perms.
And I think it's a cool look.
Maybe some kind of accessory missing.
But also with that, I'm rather careful because of all the print stuff.
So I took a moment off camera to think about what I would really combine with the cat suit
because I didn't want to bore you and as I said I'm sticking with not too much maybe some jewelry
maybe some rings and matching earrings like some bling bling here. I also think that maybe a second
look would be with crotch eye boots or something but there's a lot going on here and the pattern
is really beautiful I think it's flowers yeah probably supposed to be flowers or
some kind of plants I don't know leaves it also feels really nice and soft due to the
velvet so it's really cool I'm really happy comparing myself with the product
picture haha it looks way more see-through on the product picture so
So yeah, it's a bit darker in reality, I'd say.
Fits her really good.
But I think it fits me good as well.
No, I'm happy.
Oh, she has the zipper open.
Wait, let me check.
Like to this point.
Like this.
So that's okay.
But I think it somehow ruins the look because of the bit of exposed skin here.
I don't know.
I think I prefer it closed.
But I'm really happy.
It's really comfy.
Which is always really important.
Maybe I can add a statement back.
Because this one is velvet as well.
So it goes with the catsuit so to say.
And yeah.
It's separate.
But also part of the look.
But probably not the most glamorous.
back so to say because it's a skull which I really like. Anyway yeah I love it. Let me just think
where I would wear it. I wore a rather similar catsuit with a mesh and 3D latex printing to
party a few weeks ago in Berlin so I can definitely say that I may wear this one out as well to party
because it's cool in summer you're still like dressed but it's not too sweaty because of the
mesh which is really cool all right so i'm going to add this to my catsuit closet so to say
because it's going to stay thanks again for the gift and i hope you enjoyed this video
check out my other catsuit videos and my whole channel see you in the next video bye